Jeffrey Dahmer murdered 17 men and boys between 1978 and
1991. This is the story before that story.
My Friend Dahmer is a history, drama, crime film directed by Marc Meyers.
Jeffrey Dahmer struggles with a difficult family life as a young boy.
During his teenage years he slowly transforms, edging
closer to the serial killer he was to become.
Jeffrey Dahmer, played by Ross Lynch.
John 'Derf' Backderf, played by Alex Wolff.
Joyce Dahmer, played by Anne Heche.
Lionel Dahmer, played by Dallas Roberts.
Dave Dahmer, played by Liam Koeth.
Carol Backderf, played by Nancy Telzerow.
My Friend Dahmer is a 2017 American biographical crime drama film written and
directed by Marc Meyers about American serial killer Jeffrey Dahmer.
The film is based on the 2012 graphic novel of the same name by cartoonist John "Derf" Backderf, who had been
friends with Dahmer in high school in the 1970s, until the time Dahmer began his killing spree in 1978.
The film stars Ross Lynch as Dahmer, Alex Wolff as Derf, Dallas Roberts as
Lionel, Jeffrey's father, and Anne Heche as Joyce, Jeffrey's mother.
The film premiered at the 2017 Tribeca Film Festival and was released
in the United States on November 3, 2017, by Hulu.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, who praised its historical accuracy and
Lynch's performance, but was a box office bomb, grossing $1.4 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of high school, 1970s,
biography, based on true story, ohio.
The tone is emotional.